<?xml version="1.0" standalone="no"?>

<kickstart>


	<description>
	Grid Data Farm 
	</description>

	<copyright>
	Copyright (c) 2003, 2004, 2005 National Institute of Advanced
	Industrial Science and Technology (AIST).  All Rights Reserved.
	
	The authors hereby grant permission to use, copy, modify, and
	distribute this software and its documentation for any purpose,
	provided that existing copyright notices are retained in all copies
	and that this notice is included verbatim in any distributions.  The
	name of AIST may not be used to endorse or promote products derived
	from this software without specific prior written permission.
	
	THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHORS ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR
	IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
	WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
	DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR DISTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
	FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
	CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF
	SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR
	BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
	WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE
	OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, ITS
	DOCUMENTATION, OR ANY DERIVATIVES THEREOF, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE
	POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
	</copyright>

	<changelog>
	$Log$
	Revision 1.7  2005/04/14 22:56:32  mjk
	*** empty log message ***
	
	Revision 1.6  2005/04/14 18:24:01  mjk
	name like gfs-0-0
	
	Revision 1.5  2005/04/14 18:11:28  mjk
	*** empty log message ***
	
	Revision 1.4  2005/04/14 16:42:17  mjk
	*** empty log message ***
	
	Revision 1.3  2005/04/14 13:34:55  mjk
	AIST gets the copyright on this
	
	Revision 1.2  2005/04/14 13:18:53  mjk
	gfarm is an appliance type
	
	</changelog>

	<package>gfarm-server</package>
	<package>gfarm-doc</package>
	<package>gfarm-dbreport</package>
	<package>rocks-gfarm</package>

	<package>openldap</package>
	<package>openldap-devel</package>
	<package>openldap-clients</package>
	<package>openldap-servers</package>

<post>

/opt/rocks/sbin/add-new-appliance --appliance-name gfs \
        --xml-config-file-name gfarm-data

<file name="/etc/rc.d/rocksconfig.d/post-50-gfarm-server" perms="744">
#!/bin/sh

config-gfarm > /dev/null

rm /etc/rc.d/rocksconfig.d/post-50-gfarm-server
</file>

</post>

</kickstart>
